PATRICIO EDUARDO CORDERO ESPEJO

+56 9 7617 3243

patricio@espejozen.cl

I am a Software Engineer with more than 10 years of experience performing roles as Web Developer, Project Manager, IT Support Coordinator and Fullstack Developer, in companies of different areas, such as Industry, Engineering and Health.

I always seek to grow and generates changes that add value to the projects in which I participate. I believe that the basis of success is in teamwork, empathy, responsibility and talent that each member can contribute to common goals. I believe in good leadership, which generates commitment and results, being part of the team, as well as guides and mentors of potential talents and personal growth.

SKILLS

Web PHP, C#, JavaScript, ASP .NET, WebForms, Angular 4+,

ReactJS, jQuery, HTML5, CSS3, NodeJS (API), ExpressJS

Desktop Windows Forms, Angular con Electron

Mobile Flutter (Android), Kotlin (Android), Xamarin Forms

(Android)

Databases MySQL, MSSQLServer 2014+, MongoDB

Infrastructure SO: Ubuntu, Debian, CentOS, Windows Server 2012+

Web Servers: IIS, Apache, Nginx

Cloud: Azure, DigitalOcean

API REST, SOAP, JWT Authentication, System Integrations

CI/CD Azure Pipelines, Container Technology (Docker)
Others GIT, Task Management (Azure Devops, Trello)

EXPERIENCE

Tecnigen S.A.

(November 2017-Now)

Fullstack Developer

Development of web and desktop applications. Integration of HIS and LIS systems, for health companies related.

- **Módulo de Valores Críticos de Laboratorio** API C# NetCore, Webapp AngularJS y Windows Forms
- Módulo Tracking Derivados de Laboratorio
 API C# NetCore, Webapp AngularJS y Windows Forms, Systems
 Integration, CRUD

- Módulo Estadísticas

API C# NetCore, Webapp ReactJS, Systems Integration (PowerBI API, Microsoft Auth), CRUD

- Módulo Único de Autenticación y Autorización de Aplicaciones API C# NetCore, Webapp ReactJS, Identity Server 4, CRUD
- Arquitectura Base para Integración entre Sistemas (API REST)
 Clean Architecture, Design Patters, NetCore 3.1, Entity
 Framework, Authentication, Security
- Aplicación Móvil Asistencia Técnica
 UI prototyping, API, System Integration, Flutter

International Quality Systems

June 2016 – November 2017)

Fullstack Developer

API and web app development for Industry companies related, like Celulosa Arauco y CMPC.

- OHSAS Cloud
 - API, Webapp Angular 2
- Relay Race v1

 API, Webapp Angular 1
- Relay Race v2

Project leadership, API, Webapp Angular 2

Doctor Cloud

API, Identity Server 3, NodeJS, ExpressJS, Socket.io, Angular 4+

Derecho a Saber Ltda.

(September 2013 - May 2016)

Web Developer

- PHP (Zend Framework), MySQL, Javascript(JQuery), GIT
- API PHP (Zend Framework)
- API NodeJS (ExpressJS)
- Design patterns like POO, MVC, DRY

IT Support Coordinator

- Linux servers support (Debian, Ubuntu)
- Equipments adquisition, technical advicing
- Problems resolution

IT Support

- Workstations support
- Webapp development

Mandril Digital SPA

(Nov. 2012 - Sept. 2013)

Web Developer

- Webapp development (PHP, Javascript, CSS)
- Emailing webapp. Mailchimp webservice integration. (www.mandrillapp.com)
- ERP web

Aeurus Ltda.

(October 2011 – November 2012) www.aeurus.cl

Project Manager

- Project leadership
- Management of customer requirements
- Software design and analysis
- Planning and control

Web developer

- Websites development
- Ecommerce

EDUCATION

Instituto Profesional Virginio Gómez

(2010-2015)

Ingeniería en Computación e Informática

OTHER KNOWLEDGES

Languages Spanish (Native)

English (readed and written, improving my

conversational skills)

PERSONAL INFO

Birthday 16 de noviembre de 1982

Country Chile

Hobbies Music (Sing, Guitar, Ukelele), Soccer